A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Calendar of Events, Series 1 FA943
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Calendar of Events, Series 1
1957 September-1996
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University Press
FA943
1.32 Cubic Feet 3 boxes
3 boxes.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Other Finding Aids
FA944 Rockefeller Univerity records, Rockefeller University Press, Calendar of Events, Other Institutions, Series 2.
Arrangement
Rockefeller University press, Calendar of Events material is arranged into two series:
Series 1: Calendar of Events. Series 2: Other Institutions.
Series 1 is arranged chronologically, with one folder representing each academic year.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for scholarly research.
Scope and Contents
Starting with September 1957 published about twice a month during the academic year. Items frequently overlap.
Title varies: September 1957-June 1965 called Rockefeller Institute Calendar of events.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 537
Cell and biomolecular sciences; Medicine, Preventive; Medical technology; Medical sciences; Biology -- Research; Medical education; Science -- Study and teaching; Life sciences; Medical research; Rockefeller University Press
- Calendar of Events, 1957 September-1996; 1
  - 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1996 May 7-June 2 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1996 May 31-June 16 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1996 June 7-23 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1996 June 21 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1996 June 14-30 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - undated (Box 3, Folder 16)